https://www.askdeb.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Who’s Ask Deb?
Ask Deb.com Privacy Policy
At Ask Deb the privacy to our visitors and readers is very important. This is why we have released this privacy policy statement.
AskDeb.com recognizes the importance of keeping your personal information private. The following detail the type of information we may receive and collect during your visit to AskDeb.com and the steps we take to secure your information.
Web Server Log Files
As a common practice and for analytical purposes we collect and use the data stored in log files. The information collected contains your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider, such as Time Warner, AT&T, etc.), the type of browser that was used to access our site (such as FireFox, Chrome, Internet Explorer, etc.), the date and time of your visit and which pages you visited and clicked on within this site.
Google Ads & DoubleClick DART Cookies
In order to support the AskDeb.com website we use third-party advertising companies (including Google Ads) to serve you targeted ads when you view pages on our site. These ads use the DART cookies in order to serve you ads that are delivered through Google’s DoubleClick advertising (contained in Google AdSense advertisements). The DoubleClick cookie is used to serve advertisements that are specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The DART cookie uses “non-personally identifiable information” about you’re your visits to this and other websites in order to target ads relevant to you. It DOES NOT collect your name, address, email address, telephone number, credit card numbers, bank account numbers, social security numbers or any other private information. To learn more about this please see the Google Advertising and Privacy Policy and the DoubleClick Privacy Policy where you can review their practices and elect to opt-out from further ads.
You may also selectively turn off or disable any cookies used by this site through your browser settings, or through the settings in other Internet security programs such as McAffee Internet Security. This may, however, negatively affect your interaction with our site and many other websites. It may results in the inability to login to applications, services and programs such as blogs, forums or other accounts.
You should also be aware that by deleting cookies you have not permanently opted out from any tracking used by advertising companies. The next time you visit a site serving these types of ads, a new cookie will be created in your system. To avoid this you may elect to disable or disallow cookies in your browser.
For more information or to report a violation of this policy please send an email to questions {at} askdeb.com.
